Guide to the Medical slides collection, 1980s
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Medical slides collection
1980s
C0272
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
0.25 linear feet (1 box)
35mm color slides with magnified images of human and animal respiratory systems, digestive systems, nervous systems, blood systems and other bodily systems.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donor unknown.
Scope and Content
35mm color slides with magnified images of human and animal respiratory systems, digestive systems, nervous systems, blood systems and other bodily systems. Each slide has specific handwritten information about the magnified image and also has the magnification power.
Arrangement
Arranged by subject.
Alternative Form Available
Digitized version of this collection can be found here:.
Related Material
Special Collections Research Center also holds the
Index Terms
Document Types:
Slides.
Subjects:
Medicine
Contents List
- Tissues - 28 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Neural - 50 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Respiratory - 24 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Endo - 10 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Muscle - 8 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Blood - 16 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Lymphatics - 31 slides, circa 1980s (Box 1)
- Excretory - 21 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Circulatory - 11 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Bone/Muscle/Cartilage - 20 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Digestive - 55 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Teeth - 15 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Skin - 34 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Glands - 25 slides, circa 1980s (Box 2)
- Liver - 9 slides, circa 1980s (Box 3)
- Pancreas - 12 slides, circa 1980s (Box 3)
- Reproduction - 34 slides, circa 1980s (Box 3)
- Embryo - 8 slides, circa 1980s (Box 3)